Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Well, this isn't a good turn of events. If that's how it's going to be, I suppose it's time to get serious.
Smoke creation magic! Prison of the Fallen King!
Poor foolish little children. The thing about the Black Bulls is...
We don't lose to anyone, and that includes you! Got it?
Time to go. This ends now.
What are you?
Wind creation magic.
Engaging Swift White Hawk, paired with Windblade Shower.
He's performing a dual casting?
Time to get out of our way, Diamond Mage. The Golden Dawn will reach the hall first!
Here!
Anyone else feeling kinda dizzy?
This place is filling up with smoke. I'll wind up suffocating at this rate.
Our only chance is to defeat the spellcaster in fast.
I can sense his magic power, so I have a good idea of where he might be. If we attack, he'll most likely dodge it.
What do I know about his fighting style so far?
When he's inside the smoke, he can move really fast, and he can pick up on magic power quickly, too.
Our best shot is to find a way to blindside him. But how, when he can sense our magic?
Aaaaahhhh!
might be. If we attack, he'll most likely dodge it. What do I know about his fighting
style so far? When he's inside the smoke, he can move really fast, and he can pick up
on magic power quickly, too. Our best shot is to find a way to blindside him, but how
when he can sense our magic?
I can sense your magic power, so sneak attacks aren't going to work on me.
Whoa there! Wow, rapid fire! Getting desperate, are we?
I'm afraid you won't be able to hit me like that. It won't clear the smoke, either. I suppose
it all comes down to experience. I've likely been in more battles than all of you combined.
That went really well. You know, you were right earlier. Teamwork is vital.
どうや?
いつも僕は目を閉じては現実に怯えていたな。なんだかんだ理由付けてさ。諦めるの
Oh
Let's break down the night of the night
I'm going to turn on the light
I'm going to turn on you
Oh dear, what have you done to me?
Feeble old man that I am
Well, that's not good
Arm appears to be broken
Along with a handful of ribs, I'd imagine
I'm in no shape to fight like this
Hmm, the Clover Kingdom sure does have some rare gems
Take this diamond in the rough
A magicless lad wielding an enormous blade
Even with my considerable experience
I'd never met anyone on the battlefield who lacked magic
If I'm going to be taken prisoner
I'd rather die
Or just run away
Hey, get back here
Wait up, Asta
You're not getting away
Yes, my anti-smoke creation magic
Nothing like a ride in the hustling lazy car
Ha, I'm right on your tail
Ha, ha, ha
Ha, ha
Whoa
Aww
We lost him, huh?
Stupid smoke
You guys
We're way too fast
Man, that's too bad
I was really looking forward to finishing the fight with that old guy
But that's not the mission, right?
Let's forget him and get to the treasure hall
Wait, you're turning down a fight?
Yeah, let's get moving
There's treasure to find
Oh wow, so much magic power
That guy was strong
But there's someone here who can give him a run for his money
Everyone doing alright?
At this rate, we're going to have to forego the treasure hall
Well, I'm sure Mars is capable of handling it without me
Let's not forget
He is the Diamond Kingdom's secret weapon
Such frighteningly sinister magic
Yuno's using all his strength and yet he's helpless
Those embedded gemstones
I've heard of them
There have been rumors that the Diamond Kingdom has been experimentally cultivating mages
Who have artificially enhanced magic power
They select children gifted in magic from a young age
Subject them to fierce competition
And embed magic heightening items into their bodies
In the end, they must fight one another to the death
The lone survivor of that deadly free-for-all
Is that... him?
Whoever he is, this situation is dire
How can this be happening?
I am of the nobility
A member of the Elite Golden Dawn
One ally has already fallen to him
And a commoner is protecting me
This is unacceptable!
I will not allow this travesty to continue!
Now!
Steal creation magic!
Spiral!
Man!
Wait closer!
So...
Hmm...
So, if you leave the
A... a mineral clone?
Too close...
Quite good...
Such pitiful magic, it won't work on me.
It's no use.
I'm telling you, it's no use.
Let's just forget about training, okay?
I'm not done yet!
Not until I land a hit on you!
No way am I gonna quit now!
Asta...
Not yet!
I'm not done!
Come on, can't we just...
No way!
I am never, ever going to give up!
Stop your pointless posture.
I won't!
Move!
Give up!
I will not!
I won't!
Give up!
I will not!
You do!
You go!
Go far!
You do!
Go Fargo!
Hey, you. Freaky looking pale dude. Keep your hands off this guy.
Yuno's not yours to fight.
He's my rival!
Yuno!
You must be kidding. Just when I thought I had paid my debt to you.
I can't believe it! I finally catch up to you and you're two seconds away from being killed!
Were you just gonna let that sucker beat you?!
Mind your own business, Asta. I was this close to taking him down.
That's a lie and you know it! You're a wreck! You were totally about to die!
No, I was about to launch a very damaging counter-attack.
Lies, lies, lies!
I was waiting for the right moment.
This is just like you, Yuno.
Are you done interfering?
Excuse me?
You can go now.
Okay, I'll tell you what.
We'll fight to see who brings him down! Whatever it takes!
No! This is absurd! Three members of the Golden Dawn couldn't take him. Yet, his incredible power...
Was bested by a commoner from the Black Bulls?!
No!
Fragile, huh?
Is that... the mage infamous for having savagely beaten his exam opponent?
Luck the Cheery Berserker?!
He's the third mage sent from the Black Bulls?!
I'm being rescued by that ragtag bunch of lunatic misfits!
Mimosa!
I'm ashamed to be seen like this.
I suppose you were right about me, Noelle.
A dim bulb, just like you said.
It's true. You're rather lacking in the sense department.
But that's alright.
Because I'm here now, and I will protect you!
Thanks, Noelle.
Are you the person who did this to the Golden Dawn?!
And what is it to you if I did?
It is the strong who remain.
While the weak fade away.
Simple as that.
He can create that many clones at one time?
The battlefield is a place of power.
On it there is no room for the weak.
That's why I was born.
To destroy those like you.
Yeah? That's so.
Well...
Go on!
Destroy me!
I fully intend to.
Ooh, as again.
Spider-Man.
Hard manera...
Hard%.
They are a spawnость.
She столisi.
They've hit us until she raged,
but maybe not.
Beautifulinho is underframe.
How many are you?
Hey.
They went into theabilitation pad.
Give me over the help next time.
It's alright if you die here.
Yeah.
This is...
Oh man, I wanted to take him on.
Guess these guys will have to do.
Impossible. How could a commoner with no mana do that?
Please stop looking so horrified and accepted already.
He's powerful in his own way. Asta has the ability to nullify magic.
Nullify it? Truly?
That a commoner like him is beneath a power like that.
Perhaps he was just lucky to be endowed with such a skill.
Was it luck or something else? You can tell just by watching him.
Well, come on! What have you done already?
Okay.
Doot wants to tell you I...
Doot.
Let's go!
Tell me, boy. What are you?
Sure, I'll tell you. I'm somebody who was born without a single drop of magic power.
What? He has no magic at all? Then it was just sheer luck that he's so...
And I'm still gonna be the Wizard King. I'll fight and bleed all I have to.
But I will prove that I can do it!
Just look at his body. How much time has he spent training?
The Wizard King. Can he really mean it?
Mars, when you grow up, what do you want to be?
I... I live only to destroy!
That's why you live? To destroy?
While the Wizard King lives to protect his kingdom and his people?
We'll keep everyone in the country safe. That's why we were born, right?
I will never lose! Not to somebody like you!
You're in my way. Begone, pebble!
Sure, I might be a pebble. But if so, I'm going to be the pebble that shatters the diamond!
Just like you!
I wish...
You see?
You can do anything if you don't give up!
So let's play!
Move the «living in you»
It's not that you keep building up!
I can't obey!
We can do anything if that should be
I'm not sure what you want to do
I will accept you
We can try again
Even if I don't see it
I don't want to
I will be
I will be in my heart
Clover Clips
The Treasure Hall
We finally made it
This place is amazing
I wonder if any of this will be suitable
For my refined tastes
Okay, I'm gonna see how much loot this baby is hiding
Alright, but I want to see what's in there too
Open Sesame
Ugh, more like Pleasure Hall
Why does this always happen?
Phew, I'm all tuckered out
Run ragged at work and at home
A guy just can't catch a break
Black Clover, page 18
Memories of You
My magic is letting the younger generation clean up the mess